# Rishabh Tripathy

FRONTEND DEVELOPER

### **Details**

Raipur 07470537527 rishabhtripathy@hotmail.com

#### Links

www.linkedin.com/in/rish-you https://github.com/RishabhTripathy/

### Skills

HTML

CSS

JavaScript

Typescript

Reactis

Next Js

Redux

Daisy-Ui

MUI

Tailwind Css

GitHub

Bootstrap

jQuery

Adobe Photoshop

Wordpress

Microsoft Office

FL Studio

# Languages

English

Hindi

Odia

# **Profile**

An experienced web developer with a passion for creating dynamic and engaging web applications, I am excited to bring my skills to a new team. Looking forward to work with an enterprising team that can help me acquire an edge over the usual.

# **Employment History**

Web Developer, CrissCross Lab, Gurgaon

DECEMBER 2022 - PRESENT

### Intern, Ducat, Gurgaon

MAY 2022 - DECEMBER 2022

# **Projects**

# **Pagoda Centurion**

Designed and Developed whole frontend of the website.

**Using:-** Next Js, Tailwind Css, React-Sliders, React-Datepicker, Daisy-Ui, Javascript, Css. etc

https://pagodacenturion.com/

### Resurgent Legal

Worked with team on this website and developed various front-end component and pages of the website like :- Legal Updates, Contact-Form validation, Careers & About Us

Used: NextJs, TailwindCss, DaisyUi and many more

https://www.resurgentlegal.com/

#### ScoreME

Developed the whole front end part of the website under the guidance of seniors.

Used: NextJs, TailwindCss, DaisyUi and many more

https://scoreme.in/

#### Portfolio

Made my own portfolio.

**Using:**- HTML, Css, Javascript, React Js, Tailwind Css, Routers, react-smooth-scroll, gridsystem, Netlify, form.io etc

https://rishabhtripathy.netlify.app/

# Education

BSC in Electronic Media, Kushabhau Thakre University of journalism and mass media communications, Raipur

JULY 2018 - DECEMBER 2021

Graduated

SSC, Krishna Public School, Raipur

AUGUST 2014 - AUGUST 2015

HSC (Maths), BSS Pranavananda Academy, Raipur

AUGUST 2016 - AUGUST 2017

### Extra-curricular activities

Participated in Walk A Cause Event, Raipur Police & Maverick Events, Raipur